[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What outfits did the creators of the animated sitcom South Park, Trey Parker and Matt Stone, wear at the 72nd Academy Awards ceremony in 2000?", "correct_answer": "Evening dresses", "incorrect_answers": ["Pajamas", "Swan outfits", "Frog outfits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Nicolas Cugnot invent the first successful steam-powered road vehicle?", "correct_answer": "1769", "incorrect_answers": ["1842", "1645", "1816"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is commonly used to refer to the edible seaweed Caulerpa lentillifera, also known as sea grapes?", "correct_answer": "Green caviar", "incorrect_answers": ["Marine eggs", "Sea corn", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When running a 32-bit operating system which amount of RAM can you not functionally upgrade your system to?", "correct_answer": "4 GB", "incorrect_answers": ["3.5 GB", "1 GB", "3 GB"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Canada  is made up of 10 Provinces. How many of them do not border the USA?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "2", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Bureau of Justice statistics, graffiti is the most common form of this.", "correct_answer": "Vandalism", "incorrect_answers": ["Pollution", "Art", "Street exhibition"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1948 Albert Einstein was offered this new job.", "correct_answer": "President of Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["Head of the Institute for Advanced Study", "Head Dean of  Princeton University", "Chief of the Atomic Energy Commission"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of yoga?", "correct_answer": "Asana yoga", "incorrect_answers": ["Hatha yoga", "Ashtanga yoga", "Kundalini yoga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these literary works was not written by author Jane Austen?", "correct_answer": "Wuthering Heights", "incorrect_answers": ["Sense and Sensibility", "All of these", "Northanger Abbey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed originated in Russia and has a short fluffy tail.", "correct_answer": "Kurilian Bobtail", "incorrect_answers": ["Siberian", "Russian Blue", "Manx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Lost Boys was released  July 31, 1987.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which category did Krishna Bhanji win an Academy Award in 1982?", "correct_answer": "Best Actor", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Director of a Foreign Film", "Video Engineering", "Sound Direction"]}]